http://www.waltersanford.com/privacy-policy/

Sanford Systems & Strategies
CONTACT
CONTACT WALTER
559 S. Washington Ave.,
Why Hire Walter Sanford
Why Hear Walter Speak?
Property Tools
Why Sanford Systems Rentals?
Kankakee Information
Sanford Homes are GREEN!
KANKAKEE REAL ESTATE
Dear Walter, It was a pleasure meeting you during your recent event in Laguna Hills, CA. I appreciate the material your covered during the event and wanted to thank you for your generosity on gifting me the "Beating the Competition" sales system.
Jose U. Jaramillo,
Keller Williams
READ WHAT OTHERS SAY
Investing Forms
Kankakee Valley Boat Club Member Networking Roster of Skills/Interests
Articles
Checkout
Your Orders
GET WALTER AT YOUR EVENT
PRO REAL ESTATE AGENT TOOLS
WELCOME TO THE WEBSITE OF WALTER SANFORD
TOP LENDER/AFFILIATE TOOLS
KANKAKEE REAL ESTATE
PRIVACY POLICY
We at Sanford Systems and Strategies strongly believe in protecting the confidentiality and security of the personal information we collect.
Safeguarding your personal information
Please be assured that we will protect the confidentiality of any personal information we may acquire about you. We will not sell or rent information about you to anyone. However, we may disclose personal information to our affiliates, third party service providers or as otherwise required or permitted by law.
Information we collect from our website
Any information you enter into our website will be treated as personal information. Personal information may include your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address as well as other information. We may also collect information about how you use our website. We may obtain this information by tracking when you use our Website, which pages you view at which times and similar data through our web server software and “cookies”.
Our use of cookies
A cookie is a small data file that a website can send to the browser on your computer when you link to that website. It is not a computer program. A cookie does not extract personal information about you, such as your name and address, from your computer. It does not read data on your hard drive or instruct your computer to perform any function.
A cookie sent to your browser from our website can be used by the website’s server software to recognize your computer whenever you subsequently log onto the website. A cookie may also be used to assemble information about your usage patterns, such as how frequently you log in to the website and which pages you use, when and for how long. Tracking information we may obtain by using a cookie may also be associated with personal information we may have collected about you.
You may be able to use your browser to give you the option of accepting or rejecting a cookie whenever a website is about to deposit one on your hard drive. You may also be able to use your browser or other software to clear cookies from your hard drive any time you wish. However, deleting a website’s cookie may mean that the website will not recognize you as a repeat user. As a result you may have to re-enter information and reject a new website cookie every time you attempt to access the website.
Security of information transmissions
Information you provide when using secure areas of our Website, as well as information we supply when you are visiting those areas, is protected while passing through the Internet using encryption technology. Your browser will indicate when you are within a secure area of our Website by displaying a symbol, such as a locked padlock or an unbroken key. Encryption technology scrambles transmissions so it is incomprehensible to third parties. Although we will use all reasonable efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your information, Internet transmissions cannot be made absolutely secure. We will not be liable for the unintended disclosure of information due to errors in transmission or unauthorized acts of or breaches of security by third parties. Please note that regular Internet e-mail is not secure. To protect your privacy, please do not use e-mail to communicate information that you want kept confidential. You can, of course, always contact us by telephone or mail as described below.
Website links
Our website can be reached by hypertext links (“hyperlinks”) from websites (“third party sites”) which are not owned or controlled by us. It may also be possible to use hyperlinks to reach third party sites from this site. Third party sites may have privacy policies controlling the collection and use of personal information about you which are different from our privacy policy. A link to or from a third party site is not an endorsement by us of the site, its content, its privacy practices or its sponsoring organization, and we cannot be responsible for the practices, content or accuracy of third party sites.
Changes to our privacy policy
We may make changes to our privacy policy in the future and will be described on this Website.
Contacting us
If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please call us at 815.929.9258.
WANT TO KNOW MORE ABOUT WALTER?
Click on one of the links below to read more about Walter has to say about the real estate market.
PRIVACY POLICY | SITE MAP |
COPYRIGHT © 1996-2017. ALL RIGHTS RESERVED
